嗨  瑞秋
Hey, Rach!
-情人节快乐  -你也是
- Happy Valentine's Day! - You too!
跟罗斯住的感觉如何
Hey, so, uh, how's it going living over at Ross'?
很不错
It's good,
只不过他逼我们整天看探索频道
except he makes us watch the Discovery Channel all day long.
你知道一个中世纪的丑八怪
Did you know that something really boring happened
经历过一件很无聊的事吗
to someone ugly in the Middle Ages.
谢谢  待会见
Oh, thank you. I'll see you guys later.
-好  再见  -再见
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
那杯外带咖啡真是幸运
That is one lucky to-go cup of coffee.
亲爱的  我希望你能忘了她
Honey, I wish you would get over her.
我讨厌看到你这个样子
I hate seeing you like this.
有什么我能帮上忙的吗
Is there anything I can do for you?
你想看看我的胸部吗
Do you wanna look down my top?
谢谢  以后再说吧
Thanks. Maybe later.
-甘瑟  给我来块烤饼干吧  -你要什么
- Gunther, can I get a scone? - You want anything?
我想要的东西多了去了
You know what I want? I want a lot of things.
我希望跟我心爱的女人共度情人节
I wanna be with the woman I love on Valentine's Day.
我希望她也同样爱我
I want her to love me back.
知道我们永不可能在一起  令我痛彻心扉
And I want just one moment of relief from the gut-wrenching pain
我希望能从这种痛苦中有片刻解脱
of knowing that that's never going to happen!
我们有红色百吉饼
We have red bagels.
好吧
Okay.
蒙娜对瑞秋搬过去有什么看法
So, how does Mona feel about you and Rachel living together?
我正要告诉她
Oh, I'm actually on my way to tell her right now.
她一整个星期都在父母家待着
Yeah, she's been away all week visiting her parents,
但她会接受的  她一直都很支持我
but she'll be cool. She's been so supportive.
她甚至帮宝宝买了件小T恤
She even got the baby a tiny T-shirt that says
上面写着"化石是我朋友"
"Fossils are my friends."
少来了  蒙娜  别拍马屁
Come on, Mona. Don't kiss ass.
我得走了
So I'm gonna take off.
糟糕  瑞秋想看这卷录影带
Oh, shoot! Oh, shoot! Rachel wanted to see this tape.
-那是什么  -我朋友生孩子的录影带
- What is it? - It’s a video of my friend giving birth.
你能带回家给她吗
Could you take it to your apartment?
"糖果与饼干"
"Candy and Cookie"?
糖果是妈妈  饼干是女儿
Yeah. Candy's the mom, Cookie's the daughter.
她爸爸也叫饼干
The father's name is also Cookie.
为什么我会跟这种人做朋友
Why am I friends with these people?
菲比  过来
Phoebe, come here.
你到卫生间来  我有样东西给你看
I wanna show you something in the bathroom.
莫妮卡  成熟点吧
Monica, grow up.
你背后藏了什么东西
What's behind your back?
没什么
Nothing. Just...
跟情人节有关  希望菲比能给点意见
Just something I want Phoebe's opinion on for Valentine's Day.
-你不想听我的意见吗  -不要
- You don't want my opinion? - Not really.
少来了  我是你哥哥  问我吧
Come on, I'm your older brother. Ask me.
好吧  哥哥
Okay, big brother.
你觉得你妹妹穿哪一件
Which of these do you think would make
会更惹火
your little sister look hotter,
让你的铁哥们更想干她
so your best friend would want to do her?
红色那件
The red one.
我知道你最近很沮丧
Look, I know you've been really depressed lately,
所以我带了样东西来帮你打气
so I brought someone to cheer you up.
现在门外就有一位活生生  毛茸茸的玩物
Right outside is a real, live, furry playmate.
我不要再跟你朋友珍上床了
No, I'm not sleeping with your friend Jane again.
是狗狗
Hey, a dog!
你得承认  它长得有点象珍
Who, you gotta admit, looks a lot like Jane.
这是世上最开心乐观的狗狗
This is the happiest dog in the world.
我问朋友温蒂借来的
I borrowed him from my friend Wendy.
你可以一直养着它  直到心情好转
So you can keep him till he cheers you up.
它绝对会让你心情好转
And he will cheer you up!
谢谢你  菲比  我们一定会玩得很开心
Thanks so much, Pheebs. We are gonna have so much fun!
没错  不是那种"开心"
Yes, we are. Oh, not that kind of fun.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's!
我马上出去
I'll be right out.
我在穿一件不是很舒服的衣服
I'm slipping into something a bit less comfortable
但却很放荡
and a bit more slutty.
"糖果与饼干"
"Candy and Cookie"?
"Candy and Cookie"?!
莫妮卡帮我租了黄片
Monica got me porn?
女同志的片子
Girl-on-girl porn?!
她一定很爱我
She really must love me!
好吧  放轻松
Yeah, just relax.
我爱你  圣瓦伦丁
I love you, St. Valentine.
这画面可不太雅观
Whoa, whoa, that's not pretty.
用力
Now push!
天啊  好痛
Oh, God, it hurts!
这是我看过最难看的黄片
Worst porn ever! Worst porn ever!
-快停下来  -我在试呢
- Oh, make it stop! - I am trying!
接球  准备好了吗  去接球
Get the ball. Ready? Get the ball!
你很可爱  但脑袋可不怎么灵光
You're cute, but you're not too smart.
这是我刚刚扔的吗
Did I just throw this?
我不小心把这些跟我的东西混在一起带走了
I accidentally packed these with my stuff.
-这是谁啊  -菲比朋友的狗
- Who is this? - That's Phoebe's friend's dog.
我不知道它叫什么名字  我叫它马苏里拉[奶酪]
I don't know what his real name is. I call him Mozzarella.
你好可爱  我希望能留下来陪你玩
You are so cute. I wish I could play with you more,
但我得去上班了
but I've gotta go to work.
我希望开会的时候不会这样说话
I hope I stop talking like this before my market meeting.
对  没错
Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
再见  乔伊  说真的  我改不过来了
Bye-bye, Joey. Seriously, I can't stop it.
过来
Come here! Hey!
她是瑞秋  以前她住在这里
That's Rachel. She's the one who used to live here.
老实跟你说  我们爱她
Might as well be honest with you. We love her.
但我们不能拥有她
But we can't have her.
我真的很想她
I really miss her.
你应该了解吧  你是男生
Hey, you understand, right? You're a guy.
你曾经是
Well, you used to be.
你觉得怎样
So, what do you think?
我还是很惹火
I've still got it.
-你为什么要给我租这个  -那是什么
- Why did you get me this? - What is it?
里面充斥着尖叫  鲜血跟阴道扩张
It's yelling, bleeding, dilating.
阴道扩张
Oh, the dilating!
这是纪录生产的录影带
Is this the video of the baby being born?
这是菲比的  你为什么要看
Sweetie, It's Phoebe's. Why were you watching it?
我还以为你在情人节帮我租了黄片
I thought maybe you got me porn for Valentine's Day.
如果你以为我会在情人节帮你租黄片...
Chandler, If you thought I was gonna get you porn for Valentine's Day...
那么你说对了
...you were right.
片中的女主角
Apparently It's about a young girl
跑到大都市来追寻星梦
who moves to the city in search of stardom...
最后跟很多男人上了床
...but ends up having sex with a lot of guys.
它有四星级的评价
It got four stars.
等一下  那些不是星星
Wait a minute. Those aren't stars.
你要看一下吗
Anyway, you wanna take a look?
我现在非常没有性致
I'm not really in a sexy mood right now.
发生了什么事
Hey, what's going on?
还记得你第一次看大白鲨...
Remember the first time you saw Jaws...
你花了多长时间才敢再下水游泳
...how long it took to go back in the water?
我们不能让这卷录影带毁了情人节
We can't let this tape wreck Valentine's Day.
你不了解情况  你又没看过
Okay. You don't know. You didn't see it.
生孩子是很自然的一件事  过程很美
Childbirth is a natural thing. It's beautiful.
很美  真的吗
Oh, beautiful? Really?
你觉得这叫美吗
Really? You think this is beautiful?
天啊  难怪我妈恨我
Oh, my God! No wonder my mother hates me!
-瞧  亲爱的  -别碰我
- See, honey, there's... - Don't touch me!
-大西洋城好玩吗  -很好玩
- How was Atlantic City? - Good.
我帮你买了礼物
I brought you back a present.
你用不着这么客气
Come, on. You didn't have to...
盐水太纪糖
Saltwater taffy?!
谢谢
Thanks.
有意思的是
You know, it's interesting,
多数人以为里面添加了海水
most people think this is made with seawater.
但事实上它是用加盐淡水做的
But it's actually made with salted fresh water.
这一点意思都没有
That's not interesting.
-我觉得很有意思啊  -我也是  我想你
- I think it's interesting. - I do too. I missed you!
我也是
Me too.
-这星期你过得如何  -非常好
- So how was your week? - Good.
-宝宝开始会动了  -太棒了
- Actually, the baby started kicking. - How exciting!
太神奇了  只可惜
Yeah. it was amazing. The only thing sad is,
第一次我并不在场
I wasn't around when it happened for the first time.
-不是吧  -我还错过了不少别的事情
- Oh, no. - Yeah. I was missing out on all this other stuff too.
所以乔伊建议瑞秋搬过来跟我住
So Joey suggested Rachel move in with me.
想得美
Yeah, right.
-怎么了  -乔伊害我笑得肚子痛
- What? - Joey cracks me up.
"让你前妻搬去跟你住吧
It's like, "Yeah, why don't you have your ex-wife move in with you?
那一点也不别扭"
That wouldn't be awkward at all."
想像一下  我才离开了几天
Can you imagine, I go away for a few days...
回来时却发现男友
I come back and my boyfriend
跟怀了他孩子的女人同居了
is living with some woman he got pregnant.
你怎么跟他说的
So, what'd you tell him?
你怎么会没告诉蒙娜瑞秋搬过去了
How could you not tell Mona that Rachel is living with you?
她似乎觉得这个想法很不可思议
I don't know. She seemed to think it was such a crazy idea.
而且她送了我太纪糖
Plus, she got me taffy.
-真的吗  我从没吃过  -从没吃过
- Taffy? Really? I've never had any. - Ever?
我妈忙着计划自杀  没空买盐水零食给我
My mom was too busy planning her suicide to provide saltwater treats.
谢谢
Thank you.
你打算一直瞒着她吗
So what, you're just never going to tell her?
不  我会说的  但得先哄哄她
No, no, no. I will. I just want to butter her up first.
我要带她去吃一顿丰盛的情人节晚餐
I'm going to take her to an amazing Valentine's dinner,
做一些浪漫的事
do all this romantic stuff.
当她觉得我是有史以来最棒的男朋友时
And then just when she thinks I'm the best boyfriend in the world,
我会告诉她  我怀孕的前女友跟我同居了
then I'm gonna tell her my pregnant ex-girlfriend is living with me.
或许我之前没提过  她是个非常幸运的女人
If I haven't said it before, she's a lucky, lucky lady.
我们...这个玩意是怎么回事
So where are...? What the mother of crap is up with this stuff?
到底是口香糖还是食物  能不能咽下去
God, is it gum? Is it food? What's the deal?
好好吃  我能尝尝粉红色的吗
Oh, it's nice. May I try a pink one?
她跟我是朋友
So between her and me being friends,
还跟罗斯交往过...
and her history with Ross...
这种事绝不能发生
...it just isn't gonna happen.
那就像是你爱上了一只猫
It'd be like you falling in love with a cat.
哥们  我最喜欢的狗怎么样了
Buddy, how's my favorite dog, huh?
我最喜欢的狗怎么样了
How's my favorite dog?
你好压抑
You're subdued.
-你给它喝啤酒了吗  -没有
- Did you give him a beer? - No.
请回避一下  我们需要谈谈
Will you excuse us? We need to talk for a moment.
没问题
Yeah, sure.
是我  好吧
Oh, me, right.
-它很难过  怎么回事  -没事
- He's miserable. What happened to him? - Nothing.
-我们不过是聊了些事情  -什么事
- We just talked about stuff. - What stuff?
关于瑞秋的事
Rachel stuff.
乔伊  你害得它都抑郁了
Oh, Joey, you bummed him out!
这可是世上最开心乐观的狗
This is the happiest dog in the world.
它才陪了你半天  瞧它现在
And he spends half a day with you, and look at him!
它还在喘气
He's breathing.
我要把它送回温蒂家
Okay, I'm going to take him back to Wendy's.
别啊  它好着呢  你看
No, no, no. He's fine. Look, look, look.
快接球
Here's your ball! Get your ball!
去接球  去接球
Get your ball! Get your ball! Get your ball!
去...
Get...
天啊  我对你做了什么
God, what have I done to you?
我害了这只狗  菲比  我把它整崩溃了
I broke the dog, Pheebs! I broke the dog!
我要去接蒙娜  今晚你要做什么
I'm going to pick up Mona. What have you got going tonight?
我有个很棒的情人节计划
Oh, I got big Valentine's plans.
我订了中国菜
I got my Chinese food on the way,
还有盐水太纪糖可以吃
and the rest of your saltwater taffy.
有意思的是  多数人以为里面添加了海水
It's interesting! Most people think that's made with seawater,
-但事实上...  -罗斯
- when in fact... - Ross,
我们是一起看的那部纪录片
we actually watched the documentary together.
我的外卖来了  我去拿钱
Oh, my Chinese food. I'll get my cash.
蒙娜
Mona?
你怎么... 嗨
What are...? Hi!
你怎么自己来了  我应该去接你的
What are you doing here? I'm supposed to pick you up.
计划有变  我帮你做了特制情人节晚餐
Change of plans. I made you a special Valentine's dinner.
大惊喜
Surprise!
-蒙娜  -嗨  瑞秋
- Oh! Hey, Mona! - Hi, Rachel.
她在这里做什么
What's she doing here?
我不知道啊
I have no idea.
如果你们要找我  我在房里看电视
I'll be watching TV if anybody needs me.
她到底在这里做什么
Seriously, what is she doing?
最近  她喜欢待在这里
Lately she just likes hanging out here.
-为什么  -我觉得她很寂寞
- Why? - I think she's lonely.
但今天是情人节
Okay, but it's Valentine's Day.
-我知道  -我们能请她离开吗
- I know. - Can't we ask her to go?
不行  她情绪波动太大了
Well, no, she's way too emotional.
其实我是说  她神经失常了
And by emotional, I mean crazy!
别管我  我的外卖来了
I'm not here. That's just my Chinese food.
天啊  她还把外卖叫到这里来了
Oh, my god. She has food delivered here?
对  虽说她情绪起伏  但却精力充沛
Yes, she's emotional, but ballsy.
知道我怎么打算的吗
You know what I'm going to do?
我要去换上运动服  躺在床上吃饭
I'm gonna get in my sweats and eat this in bed.
你还以为她会妨碍到我们呢
And you thought she was gonna be in our way!
你把香槟打开
So, okay. Why don't you open the champagne,
我马上回来  我有个大惊喜给你
and I will be right back. I've got a surprise for you.
你还有别的前妻也藏在里面吗
You got another ex-wife back there?
请开始喝香槟吧
Please start drinking.
-我只是来拿电话  -瑞秋  等一下
- I'm just gonna grab the phone. - Rachel, wait.
我希望你不要误会
I hope you don't take this the wrong way.
可你这是在干嘛
But, what are you doing?
抱歉  你要用电话吗
Sorry, do you need the phone?
不
No, no.
罗斯太好心  没办法说出口
Listen, Ross is too nice to say anything,
但这是他的公寓
but this is his apartment.
我们需要隐私
and, we gotta have some boundaries,
你为什么不回你家  给我们留点隐私呢
so why don't you go back to your place and give us some privacy?
蒙娜  我住在这里
But, Mona, I live here.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day!
这也可以作为分手礼物
Or, something to remember me by.
-这次是多久  -九十秒
- How long has it been this time? - 90 seconds.
有进步
That's better.
九十秒没去想那个场景  已经很久了
Ninety seconds is a long time not to think about it.
但其实我满脑子全是那些画面
Except all I did was think about it.
我知道  我也忘不了
I know. It haunts me.
我之前见识过最不堪入目的事
Up till now, the worst thing I ever saw,
是我爸跟脱光的男仆把酒言欢
was my father doing tequila shots off the naked houseboy.
看完这个  我甚至乐意把他们的照片做成屏保
After this, I would gladly make that my screen saver.
我们得忘了这件事
We have to get past this.
我们把录像带扔掉  假装不存在
Why don't we get rid of the tape and pretend it never existed?
-这点我能做到  -好
- I could do that. - Okay.
现在我们只要丢掉这张椅子就行
Okay. Now all we gotta do is get rid of this chair.
-谢天谢地  -可不是嘛
- Oh, thank God! - I know.
请进
Come in!
抱歉破坏了你们的情人节
Hi. I'm so sorry to barge in on your Valentine, but...
但我实在受不了他们吵来吵去
I had to get away from the yelling.
蒙娜要跟罗斯分手
Mona's dumping Ross.
-天啊  -可怜的罗斯
- Oh, my God. - Poor Ross.
平时我们得看他穿内裤做瑜伽
Great, we have to watch him do yoga in his underwear,
结果现在他却把窗帘拉上了
but for this he closes the drapes.
瑞秋  关于你想看的那卷生产录影带
Rach, you know that birthing tape you wanted to see?
在我这里
It's here.
我们得在你看之前警告你
We should warn you before you watch it.
千万别看
Don't watch it.
你们看过了  很可怕吗
You saw it? Is it scary?
讽刺的是  "生"孩子的画面
Well, let's just say that it's ironic how footage
让人很想去"死"
of someone being born can make you want to kill yourself.
现在我被吓住了  你们能跟我一起看吗
Now I'm all freaked out. Come on, will you watch it with me?
不行  但我会把有我体味的毛衣
No, but I'll leave a sweater that smells like me
放在你旁边
right next to you.
说真的  你们不能让我一个人看这种东西
Seriously, you guys, you're not gonna make me watch this alone.
她说得对  当然不行
She's right. Of course not.
亲爱的  去拿录影带
Honey, get the tape.
这个动作我想起了录影带里的某一段内容
This reminds me of a very specific part of the tape.
来吧
Here we go.
好吧
Okay.
天啊
Oh, my.
-加油  -为什么宝宝要折磨那个女人
- Come on, come on.  -Why is that baby torturing that woman?
为什么这种玩意我要连看三次
Why have I seen this thing three times?
但还是很美好啊
It's still beautiful.
好可怕
It's horrible!
-我知道  我为你感到难过  -天啊
- I know, I know! I'm so sorry for you! - Oh, my god.
-你们快看   -怎么  她屁股爆炸了吗
-You guys! You guys, look! - What? Did her ass explode?
不  宝宝出来了  你们看
No, the baby's out. Look, look.
看看那些小手指跟小脚趾
Look at those little fingers and toes.
看看妈妈现在有多高兴
Look how happy the mom is now.
-瑞秋  -去你们的
- Oh, Rach. - Screw you guys!
要生孩子的又不是你们
You don't have to do it!
-怎么了  -蒙娜刚刚甩了我
- What's up? - Mona just dumped me.
天啊  我很遗憾  为什么
Oh, man, I'm sorry. Why?
从我最近的种种表现来看
Well, with everything that's been going on lately,
我算不上个称职的男友
I haven't exactly been the perfect boyfriend.
我没有告诉她  我让瑞秋怀孕了
I didn't tell her I got Rachel pregnant.
我给了她我家的钥匙  然后换了锁
I gave her a key to my apartment and then had the locks changed.
关于瑞秋搬到我家的事  我跟她撒了谎
Then I lied to her about Rachel moving in with me.
其实  我想怪她不早点跟我分手
In a way, I judge her for not breaking up with me sooner.
这打击太大了
That really sucks, man.
-特别是在情人节  -是啊
- Especially on Valentine's Day. - Yeah.
等一下  你在这里做什么
Wait a minute. What are you doing here?
乔伊·崔比安尼在情人节却没有约会
Joey Tribbiani without a date on Valentine's Day?
发生了什么事  遇上感情困扰了吗
What's going on, huh? Girl trouble?
-可以那么说  -真的吗
- Sort of. - Really?
你不必表现得这么高兴
You don't have to seem so happy about it.
抱歉  或许我能帮忙
Sorry. Maybe I can help.
不论发生了什么事  我相信我也有相同的经验
Whatever it is, I am sure it has happened to me.
事实上 我有次在做爱过程中被甩了
You know, actually, once I got dumped during sex.
到底发生了什么事
So anyway, what is it?
算了  没什么大不了的
Forget about it. It's no big deal.
-少来了  怎么了  -没事
- Come on, Joey, what is it? - It's nothing.
你连我都不能告诉吗
Hey, it's me. Why can't you tell me?
好吧  坐下
Okay. Sit down.
我很喜欢一个女人
There's this woman that I like a lot.
但我们不可能在一起
But it can't happen.
她不会是你的姐妹吧
She's not a Tribbiani?
不是
No!
她是你的同事吗
So is she someone from work?
对
Yes.
她喜欢你吗
Well, does she like you?
有时候我觉得是的
Sometimes I think maybe she could.
但这都无济于事  因为我不能追她
But it doesn't matter, because I can't do anything about it.
为什么
Why not?
事情很复杂
It's complicated.
她跟另一个男人交往了很久
She was with this other guy for a long time.
他也是我的同事
Someone from work too.
我不能对他做那种事
And I could never do that to the guy,
因为我们是好朋友
because we're really good friends.
以前跟她交往过的那个男人
So this guy she used to go out with,
还爱着她吗
is he still in love with her?
-我想应该不爱了  -好吧
- No, I don't think so. - Okay.
他是好人吗
Is he a good guy?
对  他最棒了
Yeah, he's the best.
那就跟他谈谈
Then talk to him.
-他可能不会介意呢  -我不知道
- He might be fine with it. - I don't know.
乔伊  如果你真的喜欢她  这值得一试
Joey, come on, it's worth finding out, if you really like her.
我真的非常喜欢她
I do, so much.
我没办法不想她  我睡不着...
I can't stop thinking about her. I can't sleep...
你知道吗  你得尽力去争取
Okay, Joey, you know what? You have to go for it.
你多久才会动一次真情
How often does this happen to you?
你要对自己负责
You owe it to yourself.
你的温牛奶来了
Here's your warm milk.
我要回家加点波本酒
I'm gonna put the bourbon in it at home.
说真的  跟那个男的谈谈  好吗
Anyway, seriously, just talk to the guy, okay?
告诉我结果
Let me know how it goes.
是瑞秋
It's Rachel.
你要生孩子了  你得做好准备
You're having a baby and you need to be prepared.
你得看完整只录影带  看吧
You're gonna make yourself watch the whole thing. Just do it!
我来到这个大城市  希望成为大明星
I came to the big city to become a star.
为了圆梦 我任何事都愿意做
I'll do anything to make that happen.
任何事
Anything?
可能一开始讲的是她怎么怀上的
Maybe it starts with how she gets pregnant.